

Esmaeil Jafari

FRONT END DEVELOPER

• tehran, tehran

esmaeiljafari1992@gmail.com

m @esmaeil-jafari1992

+989052672239

PROFILE

birthday 16 June 1992

I am a front-end developer with a proven ability to collaborate effectively with senior developers. I always enjoy working as a team member. I have a strong passion and Interested in learning new technologies, and using them, adhering to the ethics and rules of each set Experience working in programming teams and coordinating with colleagues

SKILLS

Javascript Git
Typescript Html5
React js Css3
Next js
Jquery
Redux
Bootstrap
Tailwind
Sass
WordPress

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Dinawin

Jan 2022 - Present

Dinawin is a company in the field of car spare parts that has several different applications. My responsibility is to move the old application forward and refactor it from the ground up.

My Responsibility is Refactor . Develop and Maintain the WebSite and also its Panel.

https://baaz.ir https://shop.baaz.ir https://karban.baaz.ir https://akorayan.com

 $\label{eq:continuous_continuous$

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Ketab Plus

Mar 2021 - Feb 2022

KetabPlus is a Start-Up in the Field Of Books Whose Target Is To Encourage People To Buy Books And Read More $\,$.

My Responsibility is Refactor . Develop and Maintain the WebSite and also its Panel.

 $React.js \cdot JavaScript \cdot ReactBootstrap \cdot Antdesign \cdot Tailwind \ CSS \cdot Gamification \cdot Redux \ toolkit \cdot Redux.js \cdot Next.js \cdot TypeScript \cdot Sass \cdot HTML$

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Sandbadcell

Aug 2019 - Feb 2021

Sandbadcell is a platform for major online commerce that connects manufacturers all over Iran directly to major buyers of products from various industries .

I have been present since the establishment of this company and I was responsible for building the site and the customer management panel and the site management panel with the following technologies and software

React.js · JavaScript · jQuery · WordPress · Css · Redux.js · HTML

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Seoraz

Feb 2017 - Aug 2019

Seoraz is a fully bundled services provider of Web Design, Development, Corporate identity, Mobile Apps along with SEO and Social Media. We use to work on ecommerce websites, CMSes, large databases for clients world-wide.(seoraz.com)

My responsibility in seoraz is to design the templates of a number of WordPress sites and to create the site and panel of the following sites: https://simagar.com

 $React.js \cdot JavaScript \cdot jQuery \cdot WordPress \cdot Opencart \cdot Joomla! \cdot PHP \cdot Css \cdot AngularJS \cdot Redux.js \cdot HTML \cdot Adobe Photoshop$

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Web Negah Jan 2015 - Jan 2017

WebNegah is a programming Company With 20 Years Of Experience inThis Field . My Responsibility in This Company Was to Design Websites According to Customer Needs.(webnegah.com)

The projects I did on the web included WordPress projects and https://talastore.com That builds the site and its admin panel

JavaScript · jQuery · WordPress · DotNetNuke (DNN) · Search Engine Optimization (SEO) · PHP · Css · HTML

WEB DESIGNER

Vira Jan 2014 - Jan 2015

vira a digital marketing site

 $\label{eq:main_model} \textit{My Responsibility is change ui and content in some Wordpress sites} \\ \textit{JavaScript} \cdot \textit{WordPress} \cdot \textit{Opencart} \cdot \textit{Joomla!} \cdot \textit{Css} \cdot \textit{HTML} \\$

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelor of Computer science

payam noor Varamin